Guide to the Cornell Information Technologies records,1940-2009.
Cornell Information Technologies Records
- Future Directions for Administrative Computing, 1983-12 (Box 59)
  Admin Comp Subcomm of the UCB - J. S. Ostrom Chair List of Systems supported by CCS Report of the Decentralized Admin Computing SubComm UCB Recommendations to the Provost
- Review of Administrative Computing by R. S. Vaught, 1983-09 (Box 59)
- CCS ( including Admin Comp Report by JSOstrom), 1983-1987 (Box 59)
- Project Ezra
  - Request to IBM from CU for Major Equipment Grant, 1984
  - Goals, Newsletters, Galloway (GLG) Presentation, 1984-1985
  - Fairs, 1985-1987
  - Cornell University's Project Ezra (Carrie Regenstein, Cecilia Cowles, Gordon Galloway), 1987-11
  - Final Totals in 1988, 1988
  - Projects Funded, Distribution of Equipment and Maintenance
- Macademia Conference at Cornell, 1985 (Box 60)
- Planning Exercises _ JWR on Mainframes, CNSF, Off Sys. Etc, 1985 (Box 60)
- Microcomputer Sales Stats, 1984-1985 (Box 60)
- MEGABYTE - NY Hospital/Cornell Med Ctr Computer Journal, 1986 (Box 60)
- CU Public Safety - Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 60)
- Administrative Information Systems Strategic Plan, 1987 (Box 60)
  Russ Vaught to Deans Council, Oct. 5, 1987
- Ken King resigns from CU; Leaves Educom - Portrait of a Pioneer, 1987, 1995 (Box 60)
- Overview of CU Networks/Networking (for CNSF/IBM), 1987 (Box 60)
- Program Conference - Cornell Computer Services, 1987-11 (Box 60)
  Vision, Directions, Statements, Reviews by N R. Scott, acting VP/IT
- Public Access Microcomputers - Mann Library Model, 1987 (Box 60)
  Text published by Howard Curtis et al
- MacIntosh Monitor (fall 87,88) Cornell Business Leader (MacEd), 1986-08 (Box 60)
- Macintosh Courseware at Cornell, 1987 (Box 60)
  A Report from the CU Mac-Ed Center
- Email - how to use email/report on status of email in '89, 1986-1989 (Box 60)
- Computer Histories: Indiana, 1986; Michigan, 1976, 1986,1987 (Box 60)
- Educom Bulletins (King articles, other or Higher Ed), 1987-1988 (Box 60)
- Alternatives for Data Communications on the Cornell Campus, 1987 (Box 60)
  A report by James A. Muir Cornell Computer Services
- A Research and Development Strategy for High Performance, 1987 (Box 60)
  Computing. Exec Office of the President, November 1987
- CNSF Six Year Renewal Proposal to the NSF, 1988 (Box 60)
- Cogger Files (Corvus, Pincnet, etc) Network Planning, Rates, 1988 (Box 60)
- Stuart Lynn - early days stuff; one stop shop, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
- OIT new organization and mission statements, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
- Administrative Systems and Data Policy, 1989 (Box 60)
  Also includes CIT Internal version from 1988 and a Draft from November 1988
- NetCornell - Gateway to Knowledge - Summary - Cornell, 1989-03 (Box 60)
  University Networking Task Force Report
- The Computer Worm - A report to the Provost of Cornell, 1989-02 (Box 60)
  University on an Investigation conducted by the Commission of Preliminary Enquiry.
- VM and the VM Community; Past, Present, Future, Melinda Varian, 1989 (Box 60)
- Tom Boggess - early days in CIT; Notes, etc, 1989 (Box 60)
- MSS Issues and Directions, 1989 (Box 60)
- Cornell Chronicle - Computing Highlights, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Mainframe Miscellany (statistics, etc), 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Hardware and Other statistics, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Academic Computing/Campus Announcements, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
  Includes list of PCs/Macs in campus locations in 1986
- Micro Miscellany (w material from Nancy Flynn), 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Highlight Summaries: OCS Bulletin, Computer Science, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- An Introduction to Information Technologies at Cornell, 1989 (Box 60)
- Selected Announcements/Indexes to Publications, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Admin Computing - Memos, Policies, Plans/King/Vaught/Koehler, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- 1980s Odds and Ends, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Networking Miscellany, Network Diagrams, Services/rates, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Technology Miscellany, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Mass Storage - Selected Items (Directions at Cornell), 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Network Timeline (supporting documents), 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Pictures for the 1980s chapter of the History, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Service Directories - CCS and CIT, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- Correspondence, Feedback, Clarifications, 1980-1989 (Box 60)
- CIT Annual Reports, 1988-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 60)
- Starts the 1990s
- A Technologies Framework 1990 - 1995 (v 0.8) and 1995 -1997 (v2.0), 1990-1997 (Box 61)
- Workstation (Personal Computer) Ownership Among Undergraduates at Cornell University by Agelia Dumas, PhD, 1989 -1994 (Box 61)
- M Stuart Lynn - Miscellaneous, 1990-1995 (Box 61)
- CIT Publications list, 1990 (Box 61)
- Information Technologies at Cornell University, CIT, 1989-1991 (Box 61)
  - A Perspective for Employees, 1991-01
  - An Introduction to IT at Cornell
- Publications Lists: April 1974 and Fall 1990 List (Box 61)
- CUBIT - Cornell University Board on Information Technologies, 1990 (Box 61)
  First Meeting Agenda and Prepared Materials on Organization Advisory Structures, OIT/CIT, Campus of the Future
- CUBIT Meetings/Agenda/Presentations, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
- Cornell in 10 Years, the Influence of Technology, 1992 (Box 61)
- GCA Migration - Foils and presentations from Cecilia Cowles, 1991-1993 (Box 61)
  General Computing (Mainframe) Accounts to Client/Server
- GCA Migration - C. Cowles and B Skoblick - session 7733 at SHARE, 1995 (Box 61)
- Merten Report - Review of CIT, 1992-1993 (Box 61)
- Merten Committee - CIT Review - Full presentations and comments, 1993-04 (Box 61)
  Including CR operating statistics for the 90s
- Report on Campus-wide Use of CIT Support and Services, 1993-05 (Box 61)
  Presented to the Information Technologies Review Committee
- Annual CIT reports: CR by Jim Doolittle,; IR by John Rudan and Budget Issues for the same year, 1993-1994 (Box 61)
- Ending off-campus regional computing services, 1993 (Box 61)
- Mainframes and Transition (to Server systems), 1993 (Box 61)
  Including CornellC (IBM 200J) Adabas Utilization
- CRUX (UNIX) use with Safety Net Accounts in CIT, 1993 (Box 61)
- ADSPAC Review of CIT ( Rogers to Merten), 1993 (Box 61)
- ADSPAC - Review of ADSPAC by members (Rogers and Rudan), 1995 (Box 61)
- IBM- Contracts, Corporate Visit, SP1, "servers", 1994 (Box 61)
- Project Mandarin - General Info and Workshop Presentations, 1994-1995 (Box 61)
- Project 2000 IBM Final Report, 1995 (Box 61)
- Technical Recommendations P2K and Information Access Architectureby Cowles in 1994 leading to P2K (Cowles, Boggess, Dimock, Taber, Lutter, Tom Young, Dan Eckstrom), 1995 (Box 61)
- Design Options for Developing World Wide Web Applications, 1995-10 (Box 61)
  CIT - Information Access project (v 1.0)
- Programmer's Guide for the WWW Student Job Postings Application, 1996-09 (Box 61)
- CAUSE Networking Awards - various papers, 1995 (Box 61)
- Blue Ribbon Commission; PC Sales from CIT to Campus Store, 1995-1996 (Box 61)
- FABIT report Planning for Learning Technologies - (2 copies), 1995 (Box 61)
  Includes organization of FABIT in 1993
- ATM and Cells in Frames Proposals to NSF by Cogger/Brim, 1995-1996 (Box 61)
- IthacaNet Conferences/Ithaca College Technology Week, 1995-1999 (Box 61)
- Cornell and the Age of Technology - VP Lambert to Cornell University Assemblies Fall Retreat, 1996 (Box 61)
- Planning for Information Technology - Dave Lambert, 1997 (Box 61)
- Project 2000 Survey Report, 1997-1998 (Box 61)
  By Agelia Dumas to assess "Perceptions of Cornell Administrative Processes and Campus Readiness for Change.
- P2K Buzz (news articles, publicity, emails), 1995-1998 (Box 61)
- P2K Committee Emails, 1996-1999 (Box 61)
- Project 2000 Newsletter, 1997-98 (Box 61)
- Theory Center and Supercomputing and NSF plus building dedication and swan song as NSF unfunds the center, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- People - comings and goings and other miscellany, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- CHAOS Corner by Dr. Chaos (aka Bob Cowles) Vol. 2, No. 1-11, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- Organization Charts, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- Computer Policy and Law Institute, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
  Also Responsible Use Policy Draft
- Mass Storage - Misc. (materials by Hanushevsky), 1980-1999 (Box 61)
- Software Misc, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- 1990s Misc Technology and Highlight Summaries (MIPs), 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- Mainframe Items (MIP ratings) (Box 61)
- Library Items, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- Space/Buildings Misc, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- CU-SeeMe Materials - supporting info for the story in the 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- E-mail Miscellany, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- Network Services/Cornell (eliminate Bitnet/Telenet, 3270 support), 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- Admin Computing Misc., 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- Miscellaneous Guides, Pubs, (CUINFO Gopher), 1990-1999 (Box 61)
- CIT flyers and brochures about Red Rover and Bear Access, 1994-2004 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- CIT flyers and brochures about computer labs and information brochures, 1996-2007 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- CIT flyers and brochures - Get Connected, 1997-2004 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- CIT flyers and brochures - general, 1995-2005 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- CIT flyers and brochures - general, 2000-2009 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- CIT flyers and brochures about Email and Mailing Lists, 1996-2004 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- CIT flyers and brochures about ResPhone and ResNet, 1998-2009 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- CIT flyers and brochures about online services, 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- CIT lectures and events, 2000-2007 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- CIT strategic plans, 2003-2006, 2004-2007, 2005-2008 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- CIT Business Plans, 2004, 2005, 2007, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- The Crisis in Information Technology Support: Has Our Current Model Reached Its Limit?, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- How to Make Your Technical Publications Click, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Revamping "Computing at Cornell" Creative Collaborations for Web Site Redesign, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Cornell Networking - Background, Activities and Strategic Issues, 1999-05 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Cornell in the Information Age - Report of the Task Force on Computing and Information Science, 1999-06 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Cornell's Flexibility in the Workplace Policy: Real-Life Examples, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- "Schmoozing at the Home Office:" Reflections on Telecommuting and Flexible Work Arrangements for IT Professionals, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- SIGUSS, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Network Cost Recovery - Task Force Report, 2001-11 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- EzraNet Proposal, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Photos of old CIT node room in the CCC building, 1980-1989 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Slides by Robert Barker, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Project 2000 and ADSPAC Miscellany, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Network Technology/History Outside of CU, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Cornell Network Technologies Info, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  (History of Campus Backbones, standards, descriptions)
- Timelines, Highlights, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- PC/Micro Miscellaneous (Anbinder slips), 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- PC Sales Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Tape Backups and Security, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- IR - Information Resources Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Getting Started Manuals - Network Identities, VMS and VMS Mail Bitnet, CMS, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Cornell Chronicle - Computing Highlights, 1990-1998, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Services, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Electronic Publishing and CUPID, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Comments, etc., Emails, Feedback, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Web Communications at CU - Dullea, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- CIT Training, Workshop Announcements, Learning Technologies, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Cartoons, etc (Box 63, Folder 16)
- ADSPAC - Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Lambert on Restructuring CIT - Town Meetings and other commentary, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Services Division - Miscellany (services; organization, support), 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Cecilia Cowles Notes-CCS to CIT; PC support; Bear Access; achievements., 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- CIT Facilities Management, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Cornell Computer Services publication lists and announcements, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Cornell Computer Services publication lists and announcements, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- IBM Through the Years from 1885-2003, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Information Resources Management Team meeting minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- The Best of Uncle Ezra, with notes, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Financial restructuring and billing, Rick Jones an Jim Doolittle, 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Information Resources Council formation and meeting minutes, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Information Resources Council meeting minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Information Resources Council meeting minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Information Project Team Reviews, 1996-02-16 (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Data wareshousing at Cornell, 1993-1996 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- Getting Started with SideCar, Thomas Weyer, 1995-11-09 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- Mandarin: Cause/Effect and workshop overview, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- CIT financial restructure, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Integrated Business Service Center, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Mandarin annual report, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Getting Started with Project Mandarin, 1996-03 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Mandarin dissolution, 1997-1998 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Minidisk Manager's Reference, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- PeopleSoft Product Deliveries Update, 1996-08-23 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- PeopleSoft software delivery problems letter from Paul Salsigiver to Fred Rogers, 1999-06-18 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Guide to Cornell Computer Services, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- "A Vision for the Nineties" CIT brochure, 1991-11 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Access to and Use of Workstations Among Faculty, Lecturers and Staff at Cornell, 1992-04 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Bear Access Interview Reports, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 12-13)
- "A Tour of Cornell Computing Services" Mike Duesing powerpoint, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- CIT Conceptual Blocking Plans and Budget Estimate, 2007-06-07 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Microsoft Word Mail Merge Techniques|Microsoft Excel Working with Multiple Worksheets and Workbooks, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Getting Started with InDesign CS at Cornell, 2005-11 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Getting Started with Outlook Email Topics| SourceForge Managing Documents| Getting Started Office 2007, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 18)